是的 我的朋友们 今天是狂欢节 "油腻星期二"
That's right, my friends, it's Mardi Gras, Fat Tuesday!
又称"忏悔节" 基督教大斋期前的最后一个狂欢节
是时候放松一下了
Time to cut it loose,
释放自己
get the Devil out ya!
我想将最热烈的欢呼
I want to send a big shout-out
献给今晚的主办人 Hamilton市长
to my man, our host this evening, Mayor Hamilton.
上来这儿吧 市长先生
Come on up here, Mr. Mayor!
嘿
Hey!
你好啊 John Cleary
Here he is-- John Cleary!
你们好吗
How you doing?
耶
Yeah!
我们都知道
All right, well, you know,
纽约有跨年夜
New York has New Year's Eve.
波士顿的圣帕特里克节
And Boston's St. Pat's
有它的魅力
has its charms.
但是没有人
But no one,
没有一个人
no one
比我们更懂得
knows how to party
聚会狂欢
like we do.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
新奥尔良
New Orleans!
John Cleary
John Cleary!
Tom 你是一个幸运的人
Tom, you are a lucky man.
你是我的幕僚长
You're my chief of staff
还娶了这样的尤物
and you're married to this divine creature.
啊哈
Huh?
市长先生 你人真好
Oh, Mr. Mayor, you are too kind.
这个城市爱你 Doug
Mm-hmm. The city loves you, Doug.
呃
Ah...
裙子真好看
Now, that is some dress.
魔鬼只在晚上出来
Devils only night.
嗯哼
Hmm.
就像奥斯卡·王尔德说的
Well, like Oscar Wilde always said:
英国作家与艺术家
"我可以抗拒一切 除了诱惑"
"I can resist everything except... temptation."
出自《Lady Windermere’s Fan》
又勾搭了一个吗
Is that a new one?
是的女士
Yes, ma'am.
确保他能在一小时内回来
Just make sure he's back in an hour
和游行国王握手
to shake the parade king's hand.
狂欢节前会选出"国王"和"王后"站着游行彩车上
明白
Copy that.
MONO要休息一会儿
MONO's taking a breather.
我的人为我订了一个房间
My people keep a room for me.
就在那儿
It's right over there.
哦
Oh...
那有什么刺激的
Where's the sin in that?
唔
Mmm!
激将法
A dare?
哦 我喜欢你
Ooh, I like you.
-嗯 -好吧
- Yeah. - Oh, okay.
哥们儿 你把电动发声器打开
Man，it's a good thing you done up in here,
第二季第五集提到过这个特别的老式机器
真是太好了
opening up the Tru-tone.
谢了兄弟
Oh, thanks, man.
为了我妈妈
Had to breathe some life
我也得让这儿重获生机
back into the place for my mama.
-她一定会为你骄傲的 -谢谢
- Oh, she'd really be proud of you. - Thanks.
嘿 King 外面有一个送酒的男人
Hey, King, there's a guy out back that needs you
需要你签收货单
to sign for a liquor delivery?
谢谢
Thanks.
失陪一下
Excuse me?
我们会为你罩住场的
We got it for you.
我知道你们会的
I know you got it for me.
我们继续这个派对
Let's keep this party going.
让我们尽情狂欢吧
Let's get down and dirty up in here.
一 二 三 哦
One, two, three, oh!
有人吗
Hello?
==GA字幕组==
本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
翻译：包子 Sally 每周三都来的鸡血 February的二月
翻译：风筝 即将达成NCIS全系列荣誉的栗子 欣儿
校对：43 师太 清欢守护者
英文字幕：elder_man 调轴：跑去看Sam和G的栗子 特效：包子没馅
总校：师太
海军罪案调查处: 新奥尔良 第二季第十四集
Dwayne
Dwayne?
Hamilton
Hamilton?
Dwayne
Dwayne...
所以
So...
某个派对 对吧
some party, huh?
有种感觉 派对才刚刚开始
Got a feeling the party's just getting started.
-开张快乐 King -开张快乐 Pride
- Happy grand opening, King! - Happy grand opening, Pride!
哦 他会很喜欢的
Oh, he's gonna just love it.
Patton在哪儿 他应该带来
Where's Patton? He's supposed to bring
Randazzo's(品牌名)的帝王蛋糕
the King Cake from Randazzo's.
打过电话了
Called.
他迟到了
Late. Ah...
找到帝王蛋糕里的
Finding that little baby
那个小东西，这是另一个我喜欢的
inside the King Cake, yet another New Orleans tradition
-新奥尔良的传统 -对吧
- that I love! - Right?
-太可爱了 -只不过狂欢节
- It's so sweet. - Only Mardi Gras
不是起于新奥尔良
didn't start in New Orleans.
而是起于阿拉巴马州
It started in Alabama.
胡说
Shut up.
真的 传说莫比尔
Yeah the lore is Mobile had
位于美国阿拉巴马州
远在新奥尔良之前就有大型派对和游行了
the big parties and big floats way before New Orleans.
传说而已
"The lore"?
在Landon Court酒店
Dead Marine and a wounded security guard
一名海军死亡 一个保安受伤
at Landon Court Hotel.
今晚那里有市长的狂欢宴
Mayor's Soirée is there tonight.
我的邀请函一定是
Well, my invitation must've
在邮寄过程中丢失了
gotten lost in the mail.
显然是的
Clearly.
是啊 街上全是人
Yeah, streets are packed.
走过去更方便
Be easier to walk.
我去找Pride 到那儿跟你们汇合
I'll get Pride and meet you guys there.
我只想郑重声明一句
Just like to go on record as saying
这不是我派对的风格
this is not my kind of party.
不管你是谁
Well, whoever you are,
都等着下地狱吧
all hell is coming in here.
绑架市长
The Mayor...
和一个联邦探员
...and a Fed?
这真是
That is,
真是一个糟糕的计划 孩子
that is some poor planning, son.
糟糕的计划
Poor planning.
我不这么认为
I'm not sure about that.
这样的绑架需要时间准备
Something like this takes time.
需要配合
Coordination.
哦 那个红裙子的女孩
Oh, the girl in the red dress.
女孩
"Girl"?
她是你的搭档 对吧
She's your partner, wasn't she?
怎么了 这些话太贬低她了吗
What's the matter-- these digs too low-brow for her?
是吗
Is that it?
她是一个... 选民
She's a... constituent.
想和我私下会面
Wanted a private meeting.
你愿意让我们怎么称呼你
Is there some way you'd like us to address you?
你有名字么
You got a name?
搞什么鬼 Dwayne
What the hell, Dwayne?
Pride
Hey, Pride?
Pride?
-他奋力抵抗了 -什么
- He put up a fight. - Excuse me.
就在你鞋子踩着的位置
Right about where your loafers are now.
丢下这个东西的人么
The man who dropped this?
我卖艺赚钱
I busk for tips.
狂欢节是我最忙的一晚
Mardi Gras is my busiest night.
我出来小憩之时
I was just taking a break
看见一个戴着面具的男人
when I saw this guy in a mask
用那个扎了他
hit him with that,
然后把他推进了一辆车
and then shove him in a car.
你看到车牌了么
You get a license plate?
看见什么人靠近尸体吗 有目击者吗
See anyone near the body? Any witnesses?
没有 死者是酒店保安
No, and the deceased was working for hotel security.
为这次市长的活动来做兼职 但他
Moonlighting for the Mayor's event, but he--
他不是我们的人
he's not one of ours.
-你是 -Kelly Grace
- And you are? - Kelly Grace.
市长的新闻发言人
Mayor's press secretary.
这位是Tom Bujei 幕僚长 还有Brad Curry是...
This is Tom Bujei, Chief of Staff and Brad Curry is--
Brad Curry 市长的代理律师
Brad Curry, Mayor's Deputy Counsel.
是我联系的联邦探员
I'm the one who contacted the Feds.
稍等 Brad 我们遇到更大的问题...
Hang on, Brad, okay, we have bigger problems--
问题就在那躺着 Tom 那个死了的海军
The problem is lying right in there, Tom-- the dead Marine.
好了 大家都少说一句
Okay, everyone just take a step back.
Curry先生 让保安封锁酒店
Look, Mr. Curry, tell the security to lock down the hotel.
任何人不得进出 谢谢
No one in or out. Thank you.
Loretta女士
Ms. Loretta?
恩 是军用证件
Uh, it's military I.D.
他是Jason Alex下士 隶属Bell Chase基地
He's Corporal Jason Alex, stationed at Bell Chase.
死因呢
Cause of death?
就是这里面的东西
Whatever was in this.
可能和用在Tate官员身上的药一样
Might be the same thing that drugged Officer Tate.
Tate官员
Officer Tate,
你能告诉我发生了什么吗
can you tell me what happened?
我看见一个穿红色裙子的女人跑过
I saw the woman in the red dress run by.
我回去找MONO
I went back to find MONO.
然后就感到脖子上一阵剧痛
And I felt a sharp pain in my neck.
什么是MONO
"MONO"?
新奥尔良的市长
Mayor of New Orleans.
那是他的手机 我知道这铃声
That's his phone. I recognize the ringtone.
市长的手机
The Mayor's phone?
对 就是他的
Yes, it's his.
-他不见了 -喂
- He's missing. - Hello?
我们认为他被绑架了
We think he may have been kidnapped.
等等
Wait--
Brody 你说什么
Brody, what?
怎么了
What is it?
Pride也被掳走了
Pride's been taken, too.
我们做了什么
What did we do?
不知道
Don't know.
可能什么也没做
Maybe nothing.
无论怎样
Well, either way...
有很多人爱我们 所以
a lot of folks love us, so...
他们肯定发现我们不见了
they must've noticed that we're gone.
怎么
What?
狂欢节
Mardi Gras?
-哦 -所以...
- Oh. - So...
这相机是干什么的
I mean, what is the camera for?
那是什么啊
What is that?
除非
Unless, I mean,
你觉得是恐怖分子么
do you think it's-it's terrorism?
是恐怖分子么
Is it terrorism?
-市长先生... -是恐怖分子 对吧
- Mr. Mayor, you-- - It's terrorism, isn't it?
嘿
Hey!
嘿 所以你才把我朋友跟我关在一起 是不是
Hey, so is that why you have D-man out here with me, huh?
-Douglas -就我们俩吗
- Douglas... - Two of us?
你是恐怖分子吗
Are you a damn terrorist?
你他妈的是恐怖分子吗
Are you a damn terrorist?!
冷静
Calm down.
我有很多富豪朋友 很多富豪朋友
I got a lot of rich friends. Lot of rich friends.
你就直说你想要什么吧
Just tell us what you want.
先生
Sir?
为什么我们在这
Why are we here?
来认罪
To confess.
Patton 有什么进展
All right, Patton, what do we got?
等会儿 就一会儿
Wait, just wait.
我等不了了
Okay, can't wait.
Pride被绑架了
Pride's been kidnapped,
市长也被绑架了
the Mayor's been kidnapped.
多事之秋 懂我的意思吗
Cats and dogs-- know what I mean?
谁在看着酒吧
Well, who's watching the bar?
一个满身涂成银色的街头艺人
A silver-painted man
还有一百来个Pride的好朋友
and about a hundred of Pride's closest friends.
多事之秋
Cats and dogs?
好吧
Okay.
市长跟一个NCIS探员
The Mayor and an NCIS agent
在狂欢节被绑架了
get kidnapped on Mardi Gras.
这不可能是个巧合
This is too much of a coincidence.
可能是有人想要传达什么信息
Maybe someone trying to send a message?
我查了Pride的手机
I dumped Pride's phone.
没有恐吓电话
No threatening calls.
我跟联邦调查局 国土安全局都核对过
I checked with FBI, Homeland.
没有恐怖威胁 连传言都没有
No terror threats or chatter.
那是他们俩都认识的人么
Someone they both know then?
也许是旧案中的一个嫌疑犯
Maybe-maybe a suspect from a past case.
我会把以前的案子都找出来
I'll pull old cases and cross-reference them
跟Hamilton交叉比对
with Hamilton.
好的 那位满身银色的朋友
All right, my-my silver-painted friend
说他看见了一辆灰色的福特轿车 车牌号是TSJ
said he saw a gray Ford sedan, license plate TSJ.
追踪它 全国通缉
Track it, wide BOLO.
公路 高速 机场
Roads, highways, airports.
好 我这就办
Okay, I'm on it.
我已经跟联邦调查局申请了支援
I called the FBI for support.
他们至少还要一个小时 因为交通堵塞
They're at least an hour out, 'cause of traffic.
等等 如果他们进不来
Wait, if they can't get in,
那我们的绑架者可能也出不去
then maybe our-our kidnapper wasn't able to get out.
正在查街边监控 寻找这辆灰色轿车
Cracking street cams. Looking for this gray sedan.
这得花点时间
It's gonna take some time.
我们没有时间了
Okay, we don't have time.
绑架的第一个小时是至关重要的
First hour of a kidnapping is crucial.
就在这一个小时 情况可能失去控制
It's when things can go from bad to worse.
你以为我不知道么
You don't think I know this?
我们会找到他的
We're gonna find him.
有人出来承认绑架么
Anyone claim responsibility?
有要求赎金么
Any ransom demands?
现在只接到媒体的电话
The only calls are from the press.
他们想在市长和游行国王握手前
They want to talk to the Mayor
跟他谈谈
before he shakes the parade king's hand.
距离握手还有不到一个小时
Which is less than an hour away.
所以解决这事儿
So it would be great to resolve this
越早越好
sooner than later.
对不起 但事关重大
Look, I'm sorry, but it's a big deal.
Curry 你是代理律师 对吧
Curry, you're deputy counsel?
你知道有什么反对市长的言论么
Know of any claims against the Mayor?
有没有愤怒的人
Anyone who's angry?
没有 你为什么认为
No, and what makes you think
这事儿不是因为你们的人
this isn't about your guy?
我们可以稍后讨论是谁的问题
Well, we can debate character later.
现在 我们最大的希望在于找到这个女孩
All right, our best chance is to find this girl.
你们有谁认识她么 跟她说过话
Do any of you know her? Talk to her?
天啊 没有
God, no!
她知道在哪里下手
She knew just where to take him.
在那个凹室里没有监控
No surveillance in that alcove.
那附近有一个服务通道
There's a service entrance nearby.
Loretta女士
Ms. Loretta?
你还在这
You still here?
现在是狂欢节
It's Mardi Gras.
我的警卫需要另一个警卫
My police escort needs a police escort
来帮我把Alex下士送到停尸间
to help me get Corporal Alex to the morgue.
不过 我在等的时候
But, while I wait,
你看到眼睛周围的肿胀和僵硬么
you see this swelling and rigidity around the eyes?
可能是被注射药物带来的反应
Could be a reaction to the drug he was given.
我们找出是哪种药物
We find out what kind of drug,
就能查到谁可以获得这种药物
and we figure out who had access to it.
我会把它给Sebastian 让他开工
I'll get it to Sebastian, get him started.
谢谢你 随时告诉我进展
Thank you. Keep me posted.
有发现
Got something!
我想这是MONO的妹子
I think this is MONO's girl.
看这个穿着大衣的女孩
See the chick in the coat?
红色亮片 就是她
Red sequins, that's her.
很好 我们负责宴会厅
Good. All right, we'll take the ballroom.
你的人负责底层
Your team has the floors.
我把这个发给Patton 看能不能确认身份
I'll get this over to Patton, see if can get an I.D.
等等
Wait!
最好别让太多人卷进来
Best not to involve too many people.
我们不想在狂欢节诱发全市恐慌
I mean, we don't want a citywide panic on Mardi Gras.
还有 在我们弄清楚眼前的情况之前
Absolutely, we need to keep this out of the glare of the media
绝对不能让媒体注意到
until we know what we're dealing with.
嘿 帮个忙
Hey, do us a favor.
别担心公关问题了
Stop worrying about the PR.
Public Relations
担心担心市长和Pride的生命安全吧
And start worrying about the Mayor and Pride's lives.
你觉得会不会是什么
Do you think this is some sort of
奇怪的仪式之类的
weird ritual or something?
现在是狂欢节 "圣灰星期三"的前夜
It's Mardi Gras-- it's the night before Ash Wednesday.
基督教四旬期首日
每个人都要赎罪
Everybody's got to atone.
从时机看 倒是挺对的
Timing does seem right.
我们应该认什么罪
Well, what are we supposed to be confessing to?
这人到底是谁啊
I mean, who is this guy, anyway?
是被你惹怒的毒贩么
Is he some drug dealer that you pissed off?
他是不是间谍之类的
Is he a spy or something?
不能确定他和NCIS有关系
Not sure he's an NCIS interest.
他在那后面干什么
What is he doing back there?
Douglas? Douglas...
听我说 你得让我来跟他聊
listen to me-- you need to let me do the talking.
哦 你看 你又瞧不起我了 Dwayne
Oh, see, there you go selling me short again, Dwayne.
人们喜欢跟我谈话
People like talking to me.
他们告诉我很多事情
They tell me a lot of things.
你以为我是怎么当上市长的
How do you think I became Mayor?
另一个候选人让你的选区毒品泛滥
The other candidate was flooding your district with drugs.
S02E06的情节
呃 我现在不想说这个
Yeah, well, I don't feel like talking about that right now.
-真的 -嗯
- Really? - Yeah--
闭嘴
Shut up!
该认罪了
Time to confess!
如果你能告诉我们是什么罪 会有所帮助
Be helpful if you could tell us what we were guilty of.
你觉得我们有什么罪
What you think we're guilty of.
对你来说只是个笑话 是吗
This is all a joke to you, isn't it...
市长
Mayor?
Douglas Hamilton 离异 有两个孩子
Douglas Hamilton, divorced, two kids--
Max和Sam 都在里奇菲尔德预科学校
Max and Sam, both at Ridgefield Prep.
Dwayne Pride探员
Agent Dwayne Pride.
同样离异
Also divorced,
喜欢睡在办公室
likes to sleep at work.
女儿Laurel在上大学
Daughter Laurel is at college.
合住宿舍 23号房
Main dorm, room 23.
你把他们怎么了
What have you done with them?
别急 市长
Easy, Mayor.
你们的家人现在还很安全
Your families are safe for now,
只要我能如愿
as long as I get what I want.
不
No.
我需要保证
I want a guarantee.
否则我一个字都不会说
And I'm not gonna say a word until I get one!
你认为是民兵组织
You think this is a militia?
也许Hamilton不小心卷进来了
Maybe Hamilton's involved somehow?
Patton没有任何发现
Well, Patton didn't find anything.
Pride有跟你说过什么吗
Has Pride been telling you something?
我 当然没有
Me? Of course not.
你比我更了解他
You know him better than I do.
是 但他也会跟你聊
Yeah, well, he talks to you, too.
Pride不见了 我很担心 好吗
Look, Pride is gone. I'm worried, okay?
是啊 我也一样
Yeah, so am I.
在心里
On the inside.
红色亮片 12点方向
Red sequins, 12:00.
噢 噢
Oh! Oh!
联邦探员 站住
Federal agents! Stop!
把刀放下
Put the knife down!
好
Sure...
他们到底在鼓什么掌
What the hell are they clapping for?
大概是因为我们仨
I think the three of us.
我们每周二晚都会来
We'll be here every Tuesday night, hey!
狂欢节快乐
Happy Mardi Gras!
你现在还能脱身
You could leave now.
放了我们
Free us.
我们没看见你的脸
We haven't even seen your face.
不知道你是谁
Don't know who you are.
你想知道我是谁吗
You want to know who I am?
行啊 可以
All right, fine.
认得我吗 市长
Recognize me, Mayor?
但你认识 对吗 Pride探员
But you do, don't you, Agent Pride?
Mike Spar
Mike Spar.
对
Yeah.
我记得
I remember.
你们俩认识么
You two know each other?
我还在警局时 我们见过
We met when I was with the sheriff's office.
25年前
25 years ago.
我参与调查一个新奥尔良警方的案子
Got looped into a NOPD case.
受害人来自我所在的教区
Victim was from my parish.
我必须去递交死亡通知
Had to deliver the death notification.
我的... 第一次
My... first time.
"您的夫人自杀身亡"
"Your wife killed herself."
这是你当时说的话
That's what you said.
我从未忘记你站在那儿
I never forgot you standing there
手里抱着一个小女孩
with that little girl in your arms.
我们在这儿是因为她
She's why we're here.
你女儿么
Your daughter?
Stacey成长过程中 一直觉得是妈妈抛弃了她
Stacey grew up thinking her mom abandoned her.
但我们都知道真相并非如此
But we know that's not the truth.
你和我
You and I
都知道是他杀了她
both know that he murdered her.
这其中一定有误会
This has got to be some mistake.
Pride探员可能牵扯进了
Agent Pride may have been involved
你所想的事情
in whatever you think happened.
但与我无关
But not me.
25年前 我还在法学院读书
I was in law school 25 years ago!
没错 还是Sigma Eta Omicron兄弟会的一员
Yes, and an alumni of Sigma Eta Omicron Fraternity!
当时他们在Alastair酒店举办了狂欢派对
They had a Mardi Gras party at the Alastair Hotel!
你的妻子去世当晚参加的派对
Party your wife attended the night she died.
我记得
I remember.
你当然记得
Of course you do.
你曾参与掩盖真相
You were part of the cover-up.
那是你
That's you.
你曾参与案件调查
You were part of the investigation.
你当时在那儿
You were there.
我被通知前往一个自杀现场
I was called to the scene of a suicide.
说是一个有抑郁症病史的女人
Told a woman with a history of depression
借兄弟会的派对来自杀
had used a frat party as a means to end it all.
我 "我接受
I... "I accept
或者拒绝一个
"or reject a hypothesis
基于证据的假设"
based on evidence."
科学家的信条
Scientist's creed.
也应该是警察的信条
Should be a cop's, too.
Hamilton所在兄弟会的五个成员的证词
Witness statements from five of Hamilton's fraternity brothers.
"Patricia的行为很疯狂
"Patricia acted crazy.
会有自杀的危险
"Threatened she would kill herself.
她跳下去的时候是独自一人"
Was alone when she jumped."
名字很熟
Familiar names.
没错 他们现在都被安排进了Hamilton的行政机关
Yeah, they've all been appointed positions in Hamilton's administration!
你认为我杀了你的妻子
You think I killed your wife,
就因为我关照了几个兄弟会的朋友吗
because I did a couple of frat buddies some favors?
宾客名单上有你
You were on the guest list!
但警察却从没提问过你
But the cops never interviewed you!
他从没提问过你
He never interviewed you.
因为我当时不在
Because I wasn't there!
我很抱歉这么说
And I'm sorry to say this,
但似乎是你的妻子出了问题
but it sounds like your wife had some issues.
-不 不是这样的 -Doug
- No, that is not true. - Doug...
-Doug 别激动 -不 我说的是
- Doug, take it easy! - No, I'm saying--
遇到那种会迫使人
Look, it's the type of thing that
做出错误决定的事情
would force people to make a bad decision!
我留在家里带孩子
I stayed at home with a baby,
这样她就能跟朋友出去
so she could go out with friends,
进行社交
do some networking.
那天是狂欢节
It was Mardi Gras.
我说"去吧 玩得开心点"
I said, "Go, have some fun."
你知道吗
You know?
接着你就出现在我家门口
And then you showed up at my door.
你在想什么 Mike
What are you thinking, Mike?
我不想再玩游戏了
I'm tired of playing games.
我知道我的权利
I know my rights.
我什么也不会说的
I'm not saying anything.
Angela Goodwin
Angela Goodwin.
前科包括 持有违禁品
Priors include possession
教唆罪
and solicitation.
你现在要犯下阴谋罪
You're stepping it up to conspiracy,
绑架罪
kidnapping,
使用致命武器袭击罪
assault with a deadly weapon,
谋杀罪么
murder?
他说那是个玩笑
He said it was a joke.
谁
Who?
有人付我五百美金
The guy who paid me $500 to flirt
让我跟市长调情 让他落单
with the Mayor and get him alone.
让市长落单
Getting the Mayor alone.
你不觉得奇怪吗
That didn't strike you as strange?
我接触过政客和他们的朋友
I've spent time with politicians and their friends.
他们会做出奇怪的事
They do strange things.
那人说
Look, the guy said
他是一个在搞恶作剧的兄弟会成员
he was a fraternity brother playing a prank.
不应该有人受伤的 我发誓
No one was supposed to get hurt, I swear.
他有告诉你他的名字么
Did he tell you his name?
没有
No.
他长什么样
What'd he look like?
灰白的长发
Long, graying hair.
很悲伤 但人不错
Sad, but nice.
他还留着胡子
He also had a beard.
我说的是事实
I am telling you the truth.
我喜欢这个市长
I like the Mayor.
我还为他投票了
I voted for him.
你的计划是什么 Mike
What's the plan here, Mike?
你有一把枪
You've got that gun...
然后呢
and what?
谋杀两个人吗
Murder two people?
你不是那种人 Mike
You're not this man, Mike.
你以为你了解我么
You think you know me?
我知道你很生气
Know you're angry.
你女儿受到了伤害
Your daughter's hurtin'.
你们都渴望
Both desperate
得到答案
for answers.
这个样子已经太久了
Been that way for too long.
抱歉
Sorry.
答案不会变的
That's not gonna change.
Pride没找我谈
Pride never talked to me
因为我没有参加派对
because I was never at that party.
你确定吗 Douglas
You sure about that, Douglas?
那是你
That's you.
你从哪儿弄来的
Where did you get this?
法学院档案室
Law school archives.
花了几年时间去找
Took a couple years of digging,
但它就在那儿
but it was there.
你说谎了
You lied.
在这个紧要关头
With everything that's at stake.
真是太鲁莽了
That was damn reckless.
Ran Angela对绑架犯的描述
Ran Angela's description of the kidnapper
与酒店雇员记录对比 没有匹配的
through the hotel employee records. No luck.
派对来宾方面呢
Anything on the party guests?
酒店保安还在看监控
Hotel security is still reviewing surveillance.
Angela提到了兄弟会恶作剧
Look, Angela mentioned a fraternity prank.
有没有可能带走市长的人是在恶作剧呢
Is there any chance whoever took the Mayor is pulling one?
我在兄弟会时 有过很多恶作剧 有些是很疯狂的
There were a lot of pranks in my frat days, some crazy stuff,
但我认为不会有人开这种玩笑
but I doubt anyone would do something like this.
-戊巴比妥 -Sebastian
- Pentobarbital. - Sebastian?
嘿 我尽快赶到了实验室
Hey, yeah, I got to the lab as soon as I could.
我是新克鲁的指定司机
I'm designated driver for my new Krewe.
克鲁是一个在新奥尔良狂欢节最后一天主持庆祝活动的民间组织
这是克鲁Livre
It's a Krewe Livre.
法语里"书"的意思
That's French for book.
我们是读书俱乐部
They're-they're my book club.
我显然是马克·吐温 这位是
I'm Mark Twain, obviously. This is, uh,
弗兰纳里·奥康纳 威廉·福克纳 杜鲁门·卡波特
Flannery O'Connor, William Faulkner, Truman Capote...
都是作家的名字
戊巴比妥
Pentobarbital?
对 戊巴比妥
Yeah, pentobarbital.
我认为是这种药杀死了Alex下士
I think it's the drug that killed Corporal Alex.
我是根据Lorretta发给我的
I determined it based on the photos
Alex眼睛的照片得出的结论
that Loretta sent me of Alex's eyes.
眼球鼓起 肌肉坚硬
The swelling and muscle rigidity
其原因是过敏反应和...
were caused by an allergic reaction...
-恶性高热症 -再多说点
- malignant hyperthermia. - More, please.
那还是一种麻醉剂
It's, uh, it's also an anesthetic
用在注射死刑的注射液中
used in the cocktail for lethal injections.
注射死刑 注射足以致命剂量的药剂使注射对象死亡的一种死刑
还有
And, uh...
我现在正式害怕了
I'm officially scared right now.
Pride对我来说就像爸爸一样
I mean, Pride's like a dad to me.
哪怕他没有意识到这点
Even if he doesn't realize it.
也许他意识到了 他只是在做
Maybe he does realize it and he's just doing
反向教养 就像阿提克斯·芬奇...
a reverse parenting thing, like Atticus Finch before...
哈珀李作品《杀死一只知更鸟》的主人公
Sebastian
Sebastian.
呃 抱歉
Yeah, um... sorry.
这种药是在配药房制成的
The drug is made at compounding pharmacies.
所以绑架犯可能在一个配药房工作
So our kidnapper could be working at one.
但麻烦在于有保密法
Well, the twist is that there are secrecy laws
保护注射死刑用药的供应商
that shield lethal injection suppliers.
雇员记录是对外保密的
Employee records are kept under wraps.
那我们不得不揭秘他们了
Well, then, we'll have to unwrap them.
有了 在海湾地区
All right, five pharmacies
有五间药房提供戊巴比妥
in the Gulf region provide pentobarbital.
我们需要调查这几间药店的员工名单
We need to check employee names of every one of them
看看是否有人和Pride或Hamilton有关联
and see if any of them connect with Pride or Hamilton.
到底
What in the hell
一个药剂师想从Pride那儿得到什么呢
would a pharmacist want with Pride anyway?
猜不到
No idea.
可能是他正在培养的一个兴趣
Could be a developing interest
只是还没机会告诉我们
he never had a chance to tell us about.
查到75个
Seeing 75 employees
有权接触到这种药的雇员
who had clearance to handle the drug.
交叉比对NCIS的案件数据库 市长...
Cross-referencing NCIS cases, the Mayor...
好 灰色轿车的情况呢
All right, what about that gray sedan?
部分车牌号为TSJ
Partial license TSJ.
-正在检索车辆管理局记录 -很好
- Checking DMV records. - Good.
如果他们之中有人开这辆车
Because if one of them drives it,
我们就离找到Pride更近一步了
we're one step closer to finding Pride.
我为什么要相信你
Why did I even think to trust you?
这个肯定经过图片处理
It must be photoshopped.
不是你想的那样
It's not what you think.
三思 Douglas
Pick one, Douglas.
他的意思是别再说谎了
He means stop lying!
别再说谎
Stop... lying!
-Mike... -认罪吧
- Mike... - Confess!
-不 -Mike 等等
- No! - Mike, wait!
Mike
Mike!
Mike 别激动
Mike, take it easy.
你可以把这个交给地方检察官
You can take this to the D.A.
不行 地方检察官在两周前
No, the D.A. rejected a request
已经拒绝重审此案了
to reopen the case two weeks ago.
起来 起来
Get up! Get up!
-说啊 -Mike...
- Say it! - Mike...
-你杀了她 说啊 -Mike
- You killed her! Say it! - Mike!
Mike 这根本帮不了Stacey
Mike, this won't help Stacey.
不要这样 不要
Don't do this. Don't.
市长要认罪了
The Mayor's gonna confess.
认罪
Confess!
好吧
All right.
我当时在场
I was there.
能接触到杀死Alex下士的药物的
Of the pharmacists who had access
药剂师中
to the drug that killed Corporal Alex,
只有一个人和Pride或Hamilton有关联
only one had a connection to Pride or Hamilton.
Mike Spar
Mike Spar.
Spar学的是医学和化学
Spar studied medicine and chemistry
在Hamilton的母校读的
at Hamilton's Alma mater.
他还有辆灰色的福特金牛座
And he owns a gray Taurus,
有人看见Pride就是被塞进了这辆车
the one Pride was seen taken away in.
用他自己的车
Uses his own car...
我感觉不像是一个罪犯的思维啊
Doesn't sound like a criminal mastermind to me.
还用注射死刑的用药来犯案
Uses a drug associated with lethal injection.
我感觉简直就是詹姆斯·邦德啊
Sounds pretty James Bond to me.
好了 他在Hamilton的母校上过学
Okay, so he went to Hamilton's school.
那和Pride的联系又是什么呢
What's the connection to Pride?
在Pride经手的NCIS案件中搜索Spar的名字
Running Spar's name against Pride's NCIS cases...
查不到
Nothing.
好吧 我们追溯到更早以前
All right, let's go back farther than that.
Pride还在警局任职期间的老案子
Pride's old cases when he was working sheriff's deputy.
找到了 在这儿
Got 'em, right here.
Mike Spar 他的妻子
Mike Spar. His wife committed...
在一个狂欢节派对上自杀了
suicide at a Mardi Gras party.
Pride的警局档案中说 是他通知的Spar
Pride's JPSO report states that he notified Spar.
好 找到关联了
All right, that's the connection.
Spar的雇员档案上
Spar's employee record
把他的女儿列为他的紧急联系人
lists his daughter as an emergency contact.
试着调查下她
Trying to track her down.
Spar在Dauphine有个住处
Spar has a place on Dauphine.
他女儿可能在那儿
His daughter could be there.
如果Pride和Hamilton还在这个城区
If Pride and Hamilton are still in the Quarter,
这是Mike Spar可能会带他们去的地方
it could be where Mike Spar took them.
我们接近真相了 我去联系特警队到那儿汇合
We're closer. I'll have SWAT meet me there.
Special Weapons and Tactics
你说谎要么是因为你杀了她
You either lied because you killed her
要么就是你在保护某人
or you're protecting someone.
哦 你现在成法官和陪审团了么
Oh, y-you're judge and jury now?
我只是个警察
Just a cop.
在做一个警察在很久以前
Doing what the cops should have done
就应该做的事情
a long time ago.
所以 狂欢节那晚
So, Mardi Gras night,
25年前
25 years ago...
救命啊
Help!
来人救我
Somebody help me!
救命啊
Help me!
没有人能听见
No one can hear you.
Mardi Gras那晚
Mardi Gras night.
告诉我发生了什么
Tell me what happened.
好吧
All right.
那天晚上我在那儿
I was there that night.
但我没看见
But I did not see
他妻子发生了什么
what happened to his wife.
我走得很早 我发誓
I left early, I swear.
你为什么撒谎呢
Why'd you lie?
那种派对
A party like that?
死了个女孩的地方
Where a girl dies?
对有政治抱负的人来说 不是件好事
Not good, if you've got any political ambition.
继续
More.
你有所隐瞒
You're hiding something.
我知道你参加了那个派对
I know you were at that party.
我知道你说了谎
I know you lied.
我们离开这里
We get out of here,
我就会去调查原因
I'll figure out why.
当时
There was...
有个仪式 算是吧
a ritual, of sorts.
不能公开的那种
Behind closed doors.
你听说过那些事情
You've heard the stories.
但要是有人知道我当时在那里的话
And if anybody knew I was there...
我就完蛋了
I mean, I would be destroyed.
你说了25年的谎
You lied for 25 years
就因为你参与了一个见不得人的兄弟会仪式
because you were part of a sick fraternity ritual?
更像是
More like
你被困扰了25年 Spar先生
you were obsessed for 25 years, Mr. Spar.
不是我
Not me.
我当时不得不放下此事
I had to put this away.
进入Spar的住处 待命
Entering Spar's house. Stand by.
把注意力放在女儿身上
Focus on my daughter.
可是
But...
Stacey
Stacey...
她却对此不能释怀
she was the one who couldn't move on.
她一定要知道真相
She had to know the truth.
我跟她说 妈妈死于一起交通事故
I told her her mother died in an accident.
但她听到了流言
She heard rumors and...
我让她别在意
I told her to ignore them.
随它去吧
Let it go.
可她就是那种...
She was the one who-who...
非要查个水落石出的人
spearheaded all of this?
是的
Yes.
她所看到的
What she saw...
她承受不了
it was too much for her.
她开始麻木自我
She started numbing herself,
酗酒成瘾
drinking too much,
沾染毒品
getting into drugs.
我必须帮她
I had to help her.
她放不下 是吗
She took it on, didn't she?
没办法
Had to.
对
Yeah.
当你被抛弃了 有必要知道真相
When you're abandoned, there's a need to know.
现在我们来破这个案子
Now we're going to work this case.
我们要为Stacey查明真相
We're gonna work this for Stacey.
Mike 你在这些档案里
Mike, what you found in those files...
发现的证据
the evidence.
Patricia的伤
Patricia's injuries--
有打斗的痕迹吗
any signs of a struggle?
警察 他们没在意这件事
Cops, uh, didn't focus on any of that stuff.
但我们在意
But we are.
来吧
Now, come on.
证明那些假设
Prove the hypothesis.
我开始给Alex下士进行尸检的时候
While I start the autopsy on Corporal Alex,
-我希望你能看一下这些 -好的 是什么
- I want you to take a look at these. - Okay, what are they?
是Brody在Mike Spar家里
Well, they're photos Brody found
发现的照片
in Mike Spar's house.
似乎是Spar和他的女儿
It appears Spar and his daughter
在调查他妻子自杀一案
were investigating his wife's suicide.
恩
Huh.
那儿
There.
割伤 颈部断裂 是坠落造成的
Cuts, broken neck-- that speaks to the fall.
恩
Huh.
这处螺旋形骨折则不是
This spiral fracture doesn't.
坠落事件通常不会出现螺旋形骨折
Spiral fractures usually don't happen in falls.
更像是 工业事故
More like... industrial accidents.
或是有人... 在打斗中扭断了别人的手臂
Or when someone... twists someone else's arm in a fight.
也许在Patricia从阳台掉落前
Maybe Patricia struggled with someone
和某人有过搏斗
before she went over the balcony.
或者她是被推下去的
Or she was pushed.
你觉得是谋杀吗
You think she was murdered?
Douglas
Douglas...
说出真相吧
tell the truth.
如果他拿走那玩意儿 就轻松多了
Well, it'd be a whole lot easier if he got rid of that thing.
我离开派对时
When I left the party,
我好像记得
I might've remembered
看到有人和他老婆在一起
seeing some guys with his wife.
仪式的一部分吗
Part of the ritual?
让她落单 把她灌醉
Get her alone, get her drunk.
她和他们打了起来
She fights them off.
我说了 我很早离开了
I told you I left early.
等等
Wait.
那个
The...
项链
necklace.
你看到她的时候 她戴着项链吗
When you saw her, was she wearing a necklace?
有个坠子
A pendant...
玫瑰形状的
in the shape of a rose.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
在警方报告里
It-it's not mentioned
没有提到
in the police report.
那晚她戴着项链吗
She was wearing one that night?
Stacey出生那晚
I bought it for her
我给她买的
the night our Stacey was born.
她从来没有摘下过
She never took it off.
哦 等等 等下
Oh, wait, hold it.
等一下
One second.
那个项链
All right, that necklace.
玫瑰... 有颗蓝宝石吗
The rose, what... did it have a sapphire?
对
Yes.
你拿走了吗
Did you take it?
不是
No!
但我想我知道是谁做的了
But I think I know who did.
天啊
Oh, my God!
这份报纸上的调查照片
This newspaper photo of the investigation.
你从盖着白布的尸体上
Well, you're not gonna get much
是得不到太多信息的
out of that body with the sheet on it.
不 不是尸体 是这个
No, it's not the body. It's this.
尸体旁边的地毯上有个标志
This is a logo on the carpet near the body
是以前Alistair酒店的标志
of the old Alistair Hotel.
Alistair 我从没听过
The Alistair-- I never heard of it.
是 因为它很多年前就关了
Yeah, 'cause it closed years and years ago.
老板拆毁了酒店 但有一部分完整保留了
The owners gutted it, but left some of it intact.
他们在这个地方建了什么
What did they build in its place?
原址和附近建造了Landon Court酒店
The Landon Court Hotel on top of and around it.
那正是市长派对的举办地
That's-that's where the Mayor's party is.
没人能够弄明白
And no one can figure out
Spar是怎么把市长带走的
how Spar got the Mayor out of there.
如果他们没有离开过呢
What if they never left?
他以某种方式控制了市长
He-he-he somehow restrains the Mayor,
然后去抓Pride
goes and gets Pride,
再回到犯罪现场
then returns to the scene of the crime.
她妻子25年前去世的地方
Where his wife died 25 years ago.
Sebastian
Sebastian...
我觉得Hamilton和Pride
I think Hamilton and Pride
还在那家酒店的某个地方
are still somewhere in that hotel.
直到他说起项链
I... I didn't make the connection
我才联系起来的
till he said the thing about the necklace.
几年前 我和几个人在打扑克牌
A couple years ago, I was playing poker with some guys.
兄弟会的吗
Fraternity brothers?
其中有个人说起一条项链
And one of them talked about a necklace.
将其称为他的战利品
Called it his trophy.
说它代表了 只要你认识对的人
Said it represented what you can get away with
你就可以逍遥法外
if you know the right people.
你知道项链在哪儿吗
You know where the necklace is?
恩
Uh-huh.
谁拿了它
Who has it?
谁杀了我老婆
Who killed my wife?
你先放了我们
Not until you let us go.
Douglas
Douglas!
不要讨价还价
Not a negotiation!
谁拿着它
Who has it?!
告诉我
Tell me!
不然Pride探员就得死
Or Agent Pride dies.
这是以前Alistair酒店的地图
This map is of the old Alistair Hotel.
酒店里的酒店么
A... a hotel within a hotel?
这是验尸员的推论吗
This is the medical examiner's theory?
你有更好的想法吗
You got a better one?
Spar付钱给女孩
All right, Spar pays the girl.
她去勾引Hamilton
And she lures Hamilton.
然后Spar袭击他
And then Spar attacks him
把他拉进服务通道
and pulls him into this service entrance.
对 所以储藏室就是
All right, so the storage closet where
Alex下士尸体被发现的地方 看上去
Corporal Alex's body was found, it looks like
在这儿后面有什么通道
there's some kind of tunnel behind it.
但解释不了Spar是怎么抓住Pride探员的
But that doesn't explain how Spar got to Agent Pride.
这可能是... Patton最终发现一个线索
This might-- Patton finally got a hit
这辆灰色轿车离开了酒吧
on the gray sedan seen leaving the bar.
停在麦迪逊大街
It's parked on Madison Street.
那儿有一个旧的服务通道
Well, there's an old service entrance there.
对
Yep.
Spar控制住了Hamilton
Spar restrains Hamilton,
由服务通道离开 去抓Pride
leaves through the service entrance to get Pride,
把他带回来 趁着狂欢节的混乱
brings him back, chaos of Mardi Gras,
没有人知道
no one's the wiser.
计划还算完美
It was kind of the perfect plan.
为了什么 把Pride和市长
To what-- taking Pride and the Mayor
带回他妻子自杀的地点
back to the scene of his wife's suicide?
那人脑子有病
Guy's a psychopath.
我们得把事情处理好
Okay, we got to do this right.
有什么人是这家伙信任的 家人有吗
Is there anybody this guys trusts? Family?
如果他跟我们联系了 我们找谁去跟他谈
Anyone we can get to talk to him, if he makes contact?
他有个女儿 我们正试图和她取得联系
He's got a daughter and we are trying to get in touch with her.
你需要我
You need me.
要我帮忙 就不能伤害他
And I'm not doing anything without him.
说吧
Tell me.
听着 Mike
Listen, Mike...
我的确不是一个好父亲
God knows I'm no authority on parenting.
但从你身上 我能学到一些事
But I could learn a thing or two from you.
真的
Yeah.
比方说 把孩子的幸福放在首位
Like putting my kid's welfare before mine.
正如你为Stacey所做的一样
Just like you did with Stacey.
够了
Stop.
她就是我们此刻在这里的原因
She's the reason why we're here now.
她也是你必须放我们走的理由
And she's the reason why you need to let us go.
别说了
Stop.
你不想再见到Stacay吗
Don't you want to see Stacey again?
我再也见不到她了
Never gonna see her again.
为什么
Why not?
她死了 对吗
She's dead, isn't she?
坏消息
Bad news.
Spar的女儿因吸毒过量而死
Spar's daughter died of a drug overdose.
什么时候
When?
两个礼拜前
Two weeks ago.
好吧 谢谢
All right, thanks.
他女儿死了 吸毒过度
Daughter's dead. Drug overdose.
没有家人可以说服Spar了吗
So no family to talk Spar down?
没了 只能靠我们自己
Nope, it's up to us.
Percy和我负责地道
All right, Percy and I will take the tunnel.
Tate 你负责服务通道
Tate, you got the service entrance.
明白
Copy.
他就没打算放我们走
He was never gonna let us go.
改变计划
Change the plan.
从一开始就是自杀性任务
It's been a suicide mission from the start.
改变计划 Douglas
Change it, Douglas.
怎么变
How?
谁拿了项链
Who has the necklace?
谁杀了Patricia
Who killed Patricia?
名字 告诉他
A name-- give him...
告诉他名字
give him a name.
政治自杀 Dwayne
Political suicide, Dwayne.
实实在在的自杀
An actual suicide.
那玩意儿开着 我是什么也不会说的
And I am not saying a word with that thing on.
你这个自私的混蛋
You selfish son of a bitch!
我会查清楚的 Douglas
I'll figure it out, Douglas.
如果我们能够离开 你知道我一定会的
We get out of here... you know I will.
你知道我一定会的
You know I will!
Lasalle探员 我就快到了
Agent Lasalle, I'm closing the gap.
就是这里
This is it.
从这里下去
Down there.
开始行动
Let's roll.
让我看看照片
Let me see the picture.
左边第四个人
Fourth guy from the left.
-Tate -已就位
- Tate? - In position.
她要的就是这个
All she wanted.
真正需要的
Needed, really.
你觉得她知道我们抓住他了吗
You think she knows we got him?
是
Yes.
我相信她知道了
I believe she does.
她们都知道了
They both do.
Dwayne 帮我松开
Dwayne, cut me loose.
NCIS
NCIS!
-把手举起来 -不不不 我们很安全
- Get your hands up! - No, no, no, we're clear!
-枪 -不
- Gun! - No!
Pride
Pride!
Pride Pride 你受伤了吗
Pride! Pride, are you hurt?
你中枪了么
You hit?
回答我
Talk to me!
你能坐起来吗
Look, can you sit up?
那是摄像机 不是枪
It was a camera, not a gun.
他只想做一个好父亲
He was just trying to be a good dad.
市长
Mayor...
你确定能继续参加狂欢夜吗
You're sure you're okay to continue with the night?
我看起来不行吗 Tom
Don't I look okay, Tom?
你看起来非常好
You look great!
英俊潇洒
Handsome.
-甚至是焕然一新 -谢谢你 Kelly
- Refreshed, even. - Thank you, Kelly.
希望我也如此 先生
If I may so, sir.
-谢谢 -先生 游行国王
- Thank you. - Sir, the parade king
还有三分钟 你要和他握手
three minutes-- gotta shake his hand.
好 好 就一会 一会儿
Yeah, yeah, uh, just one sec. One second.
马上回来
Be right back.
嘿 Dwayne
Hey, Dwayne?
我以为你会离开
Well, I thought you'd be off
去庆祝你的开业大典
celebrating your grand opening.
你促成了一个很糟糕的结局 Douglas
You let it get awfully close there, Douglas.
尽管如此 但我救了你的命
I saved your life, nonetheless.
是可以这么说
You could say that.
录像在哪儿
Where's the video?
安全的地方
It's safe.
恩
Mm.
我希望销毁它 Dwayne
Well, I want it destroyed, Dwayne.
狂欢节快乐 市长先生
Happy Mardi Gras, Mr. Mayor.
你也是
You, too.
Bujei女士
Ms. Bujei?
这条项链非常漂亮
That is a very pretty necklace.
是你丈夫送的礼物吗
Is it a gift from your husband?
我怎么感觉
Why do I get the feeling you already
你已经知道答案了
know the answer to that question?
Tom 怎么了
Tom, what is going on here?
这些警官想问他几个问题
These officers want to ask him some questions
关于Patricia Spar女士的谋杀案
about the murder of Patricia Spar.
嗨 各位 看看我们找到了谁
Hey, everybody, look who we found!
爸
Dad!
呃
Well...
他
uh, he was
有点担心你
a little worried about you.
我也是
As was I.
多谢来救我 伙计
Thanks for finding me, boo.
嘿 Patton
Hey, Patton!
老伙计 老伙计
My man, my man!
嘿
Yeah, hey...
我们一直为你留着这个
we have been saving this for you, man.
"我们"吗 是我吧
"We"? I.
他忍不住要对这东西下手
He couldn't keep his hands off this thing.
三人夹击
Triple teaming.
别啊 伙计
Come on, man.
怎么能这么说
Is that right?
吃到那个小东西的人
Whoever gets the baby
蛋糕里面有一个小陶瓷国王，吃到代表幸运
明年会拥有
has health and prosperity
健康和成功
for the next year.
好 是我想要的
All right, well, it sounds good to me.
算我一个
I'm in.
翻译：包子 Sally 每周三都来的鸡血 February的二月
翻译：风筝 即将达成NCIS全系列荣誉的栗子 欣儿
校对：43 师太 清欢守护者
总校：师太 英文字幕：elder_man
调轴：跑去LA看SG的栗子（栗栗） 特效：包子
市长的肺活量真牛， 喊救命时候杠杠的~
这集爆炸呀。King居然被绑了！一开始还以为是民兵组织呢！
OZ的粉呢！神剧OZ的粉们看到Spar有没有一种莫名的熟悉感。
King不在熊孩子开始接手了233333熊孩子发现King被绑了不要太着急。
第一季开始每次我以为市长要黑了，最后都能洗白....神奇呀。
LaSalle最后看到King那里，以为King中弹了，太心疼了。
这次标题"Fathers' Day"父亲节，嘛，熊儿子和King也很符合嘛
没有King的指挥和带领，这个team办案也是有条不紊
LaSalle神萌！我们每周二都来